const hardQuestions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is the square of 4?",
        answer: 16,
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is the cube root of 27?",
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is square of 11?",
        answer: 121,
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is 15 * 6?",
        answer: 90,
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What is 15*15?",
        answer: 225,
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What is square of 12?",
        answer: 144,

    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What is cube of 5?",
        answer: 125,

    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What is square root of 81?",
        answer: 9,

    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What is square of 13?",
        answer: 169,

    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What is cube of 3?",
        answer: 27,

    },
];

export default hardQuestions;
